Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Communist and Socialist Serials TAM.747
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: American Publications, 1881-2010; 68.4 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 102 flat boxes
  - Unity Supplement / Suplemento De La Unidad: U.S. League of Revolutionary Struggle / Getting Together Publications, San Francisco, CA, 1978; cuid12475 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Bolshevik: U.S. Leninist Core, Bronx, NY, 1978-1978; cuid12476 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin: U.S.-Soviet Workers Information Committee, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - Struggle at UCS: UCS, 1972; cuid12477 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - "Creeping Socialism" Vs. Limping Capitalism: Union for Democratic Socialism, New York, NY, circa 1950s; cuid12478 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Reading Lists in Radical Political Economics: Union for Radical Political Economics, New York, NY, 1977; cuid12479 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Information Bulletin: Union of the Soviet Socialist Republics, Washington, DC, 1945; cuid12481 (Box 79, Folder 18, Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Why we are in Prison: Union Labor, US, 1944; cuid12480 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Der Hammer: Union Square Press, New York, NY, 1928 (Box 227, Folder 1-2)
  - NDM Bulletin: United Auto Workers, St. Louis, MO, 1993; cuid12482 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin of the United Committee of South Slavic Americans: United Committee of South Slavic Americans, New York, NY, 1946; cuid12483 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Communist: United Communist Party of America, Detroit, MI, 1920; cuid12484 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Party Building and the Main Danger: An Exchange Between the Proletarian Unity League and The Committee of Five: United Labor Press, New York, NY, 1978; cuid12485 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Campus Socialist: United Office and Professional Workers of America-CIO, Chicago, IL, 1938; cuid12486 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Resistance: United Revolutionary Organisation, circa 1970s; cuid12487 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Hearings Before the Committee on Un-American Activities House of Representatives: United States Government Printing Office, Washington, DC, 1948; cuid12488 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Strategy and Tactics of World Communism: United States Senate, Washington, DC, 1955 (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Struggle: United Struggle Press, New York, NY, 1977; cuid12489 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Movement: United Workers Party, New York, NY, 1989; cuid12490 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - UNITY: UNITY, Oakland, CA, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Unity: Unity Publications, Oakland, CA, 1988-1989 (Box 213, Folder 12-15, Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Critique of the RWH's "Realignment, Reagan and Our Tasks": US League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L), Oakland, CA, 1981; cuid12491 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - RWH on the Black Liberation Movement: Wrong Again!: US League of Revolutionary Struggle (M-L), 1981; cuid12492 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - African Studies by Soviet Scholars: USSR Academy of Sciences, Moscow, Russia, 1981-1983 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Information Bulletin on Cultural Life in USSR: USSR Society of Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, 1925; cuid12493 (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - Rebel Youth: Vanguard Jrs., New York, NY, 1934; cuid12494 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Lenin und der Leninismus: Verlag Fur Literatur und Politik Wien VIII, circa 1940s; cuid12495 (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - Communist Viewpoint: A Youth and Student Publication: Viewpoint, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid12496 (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Studies in Comparative Communism: Von KleinSmid Institute of International Affairs, 1970, 1973-1974, 1976-1977; cuid12497 (Box 164, Folder 1-3)
  - Activist: W. E. B. DuBois Clubs of New York, New York, NY, 1966-1968 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Spark: Washington Area Spark, Takoma Park, MD, circa 1970s; cuid12498 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Wisconsin Patriot: Wisconsin Alliance, Madison, WI, 1970-1976; cuid12499 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Wisconsin Leader: Wisconsin Leader Publishign Company, Milwaukee, WI, 1934; cuid12500 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Review: Wm. S. Ainsworth, Birmingham, AL, 1951; cuid12501 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - Women's Educational League: Women's Educational League, 1949; cuid12502 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - Worker for the Northwest: Worker, New York, NY, 1975, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1979; cuid12503 (Box 173, Folder 5-8)
  - On the Line: Worker Unity Organization, St. Louis, MO, 1974-1975; cuid12504 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - General Strike and the General Betrayal: Workers (Communist) Party of America/The Daily Worker Publishing Co., 1926; cuid12505 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - Bayou Worker: Workers Against Capitalism, New Orleans, LA, 1998; cuid12506 (Box 163, Folder 21)
  - People's Front Illusion: Workers Age Publishers, circa 1960s; cuid12507 (Box 163, Folder 22)
  - Workers Alliance News: Workers Alliance of Essex County, Newark, NJ, 1938; cuid12508 (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - Workers Democracy = Democracia Obrera: Workers Democracy Network, Trenton, NJ, 2001; cuid12509 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Action: Workers International League, 1945; cuid12510 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Communism Versus Fascism: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1941; cuid12511 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party in Action: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1932; cuid12512 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Communist Party of the United States of America: Workers Library Publishers, 1938; cuid12513 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Fight Against Hitlerism: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1941; cuid12514 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Going Left: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1936; cuid12515 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Inside Italy: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1942; cuid12516 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - Meaning of the Soviet Trials: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1938; cuid12517 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - People and the Congress: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid12518 (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Program of the Communist International: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1936; cuid12519 (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Real Father Coughlin: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1939; cuid12520 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Real Huey P. Long: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12521 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Road to Negro Liberation: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1934; cuid12522 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Truth About Father Coughlin: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12523 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Two Questions on Winning the War: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1942; cuid12524 (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - U.S.A and the U.S.S.R: War Allies and Friends: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1942; cuid12525 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Why Hearst Lies About Communism: Three Open Letters to Wiliam Randolph Hearst: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12526 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Women - Vote for Life!: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1940; cuid12527 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Women in the Soviet Union: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1938; cuid12528 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - China: The March Toward Unity: Workers Library Publishers, Inc., New York, NY, 1937; cuid12529 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Economics of Communism: Soviet Economy in its World Relation: Workers Library Publishers, Inc., New York, NY, 1939; cuid12530 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Rise of Socialism in the Soviet Union: Workers Library Publishers/ The 7th World Congress of the Communist International, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12531 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Resolutions - Seventh Congress of the Communist International: Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1935 (Box 233, Folder 18)
  - Organization Bulletin: Workers Party New York, New York, NY, 1935 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Acceptance Speeches - Communist Candidates in the Presidential Elections: Workers Library Publishers/ The National Campaign Committee of the Communist, New York, NY, 1936; cuid12532 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Bulletin: Workers Party, 1941-1942 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Party Builder: Workers Party, New York, NY, 1946-1948; cuid12533 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Plenty for All: The Meaning of Socialism: Workers Party, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid12534 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Proletarian Socialism: Workers Party for Proletarian Socialism Publications, San Francisco, CA, 1977; cuid12535 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Struggle: Workers' Party of Jamaica, 1984-1985; cuid12536 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - International Workers School: Workers Party of the United States, New York, NY, circa 1950s; cuid12537 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - War and the Workers: Workers Party of the United States, circa 1940s; cuid12538 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - The Question of Unity Between the Workers Party and the Socialist Workers Party: Workers Party Publications, Long Island City, NY, 1947; cuid12539 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Sing!: Labor and Socialist Songs: Workers Party, Los Angeles Section, Los Angeles, CA, 1945; cuid12540 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - City Convention reports and bulletins: Workers Party, New York Local, New York, NY, 1943-1945; cuid13380 (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - Worker: Workers Party, U.S.A., Chicago, IL, 2001-2002; cuid12541 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - What to Read - Popular Reading List for Workers - A Reading Guide for New Party Members: Workers Party/ National Educational Department Workers Party, circa 1950s; cuid12542 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Blue Cover Series / Study Outline: Workers Pary, U.S.A., circa 1940s; cuid12543 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Workers' Power Discussion Bulletin: Workers' Power, 1980-1983; cuid12544 (Box 172, Folder 9-11)
  - Workers Press: Workers Revolutionary Party, 1992; cuid12545 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Workers Review: Workers Socialist League, San Francisco, CA, 1987; cuid12546 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - Fight for the real emancipation of women! / Luchen por la verdadera liberacion de mujeres: Workers Viewpoint Organization, New York, NY, 1977; cuid12547 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Workers Viewpoint Supplement: Workers Viewpoint Organization, New York, NY, 1977; cuid12548 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Workers' Voice: Workers' Voice, Detroit, MI, 1997; cuid12549 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Liberation & Marxism: Workers World, New York, NY, 1997; cuid12550 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Fight to Win: Worker-Student Alliance Caucus - Students for Democratic Socialism, Flushing, NY, 1969; cuid12551 (Box 151, Folder 3, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 15)
  - Working People's News: Working People's News, New York, NY, 1988-1997; cuid12552 (Box 129, Folder 1-3, Box 223, Folder 16)
  - World Newsletter: World Newsletter, New York, NY, 1953; cuid12553 (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - World Socialist Catalogue: World Socialist Party, Boston, MA, circa 1980s; cuid12554 (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - Workers World Newspaper: WW Publishers, New York, NY, 1992; cuid12555 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Clarity: Young Communist League, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - Election Message to All Young People of New York: Young Communist League, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid12556 (Box 169, Folder 47)
  - Extracts and Resolutions: Young Communist League, New York, NY, 1937; cuid12557 (Box 146, Folder 18)
  - Jersey Youth Vote for a Future: Young Communist League, Newark, NJ, 1900; cuid12558 (Box 169, Folder 48)
  - Young Communist League Builder: Young Communist League, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12559 (Box 169, Folder 49, Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Programme of the Young Communist International: Young Communist League of America, New York, NY, 1929; cuid12560 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Year Book: Young Communist League of America, 1937; cuid12561 (Box 169, Folder 50)
  - YCL Elevator: Young Communist League, U.S.A., Chicago, IL, 1986; cuid12562 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Life with a Purpose: Why You Should Join the Young Communist League: Young Communist League, USA, New York, NY, circa 1950s; cuid12563 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Red Letter: Young Democratic Socialists, New York, NY, 1999; cuid12564 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - YSR: Young People's Socialist Leagues (YPSL), Chicago, Illinois, 1971; cuid13340 (Box 199, Folder 17)
  - Communist China - A Socialist Analysis: Young Peoples Socialist League, New York, NY, 1962; cuid12565 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Laos: Young Peoples Socialist League, New York, NY, 1962; cuid12566 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - State Bulletin: Young Peoples Socialist League, Boston, MA, 1936; cuid12567 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Yanqui No! Castro No! Cuba Si!: Young Peoples Socialist League, 1962; cuid12568 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - "Out of Their Own Mouths": Young People's Socialist League, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid12569 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Leon Sedov:Son, Friend, Fighter: Young People's Socialist League, New York, NY, 1938; cuid12570 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Outline of Socialist Economics: Young People's Socialist League, Chicago, IL, circa 1950s; cuid12571 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Currents: Young People's Socialist League, New York, NY, 1975; cuid12572 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Currents: Young People's Socialist League, New York, NY, 1976; cuid12573 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Currents: Young People's Socialist League, New York, NY, 1976; cuid12574 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Youth Want Jobs: Young People's Socialist League, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid12575 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy's Alliance for Progress: Young Peoples Socialist League, Princeton Chapter, New York, NY, 1962; cuid12576 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Rosa Luxemburg: Selections from her works: Young People's Socialist League/ National Education Committee, Chicago, IL, 1946; cuid12577 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Together: Young Progressives of America (YPA), New York, NY, 1950; cuid12578 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Young Red: Young Red, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - Young Social Democrat: Young Social Democrats, Washington, DC, circa 1990s; cuid12579 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Malcolm X Talks to Young People: Young Socialist, New York, NY, 1965; cuid12580 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Fight Against Racism: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1975; cuid12581 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Nixon Versus the Student Movement: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1970; cuid12582 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Organizing the YSA: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1974-1976; cuid12583 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Organizing the YSA: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1975-1976; cuid12584 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Organizing the YSA Part 2: Financial handbook 'What is Socialism' class series: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1975; cuid12585 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Revolutionary Student Movement: Theory and Practice: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12586 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Young Socialist Alliance Internal Information Bulletin: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1971, 1976-1977; cuid12587 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Young Socialist Organizer: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1972; cuid12588 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - YSA Builder: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1965; cuid12589 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - YSA Information Bulletin: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12590 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - YSA International Information Bulletin: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12591 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Maoism in the US: A Critical History of the Progressive Labor Party: Young Socialist Alliance/Merit Publishers, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12592 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - How a Minority Can Change Society: Young Socialist Forum, New York, NY, 1964; cuid12593 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Young Socialist Challenge: Young Socialist League, 1954; cuid12594 (Box 121, Folder 6, Box 218, Folder 10)
  - National Office Bulletin: Young Socialists, 1953; cuid12595 (Box 78, Folder 30, Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Young Socialist: Young Socialists, New York, NY, 1973-1981, 1983-1984; cuid12596 (Box 121, Folder 4-5)
  - National Office Newsletter: Young Socialists (YPSL), 1953; cuid12597 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Everything you Always Wanted to Know About Geroge McGovern: Young Socialists for Jenness and Pulley, 1969; cuid12598 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Young Worker Drive Bulletin: Young Worker, New York, 1935; cuid12599 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - The Communist Youth International: Report of Activity Between the 4th and 5th Congress: Young Workers (Communist) League of America, New York, NY, 1928 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - First Congress Communist Youth of Greece: Young Workers Liberation League, New York, NY, 1976; cuid12600 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Year Book: Young Communist League, New York State, New York, NY, 1938 (Box 248, Folder 11, Box 169, Folder 50)
  - Proceedings of the Twenty-Fourth National Convention of the Young Peoples Socialist League: Young Peoples Socialist League, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960 (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - International Youth Information Bulletin: Young Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - New York Section Notes: Young Workers Liberation League, New York, NY, 1980; cuid12601 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Trotskyism, the Inside Job: An Analysis of the Young Socialist Alliance: Young Workers Liberation League, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12602 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Youth for Derry & Shaw Campaigner: Youth for Derry & Shaw, New York, NY, 1964; cuid12603 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Young Red: National Communist Youth Newsletter: Youth In Action, 1977; cuid12604 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Worldwide Youth Radicalization and the Tasks of the Fourth International: Youth Socialist Alliance, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12605 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Memo to the YPSL Membership: YPSL National Office, NY, 1953; cuid12606 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Industrijalist: Yugoslav Industrial Socialist Alliance, Detroit, MI, 1929; cuid12607 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Bulletin on the Negro Question, circa 1950s; cuid12608 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Class Struggle, 1979; cuid12609 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - Di Socialistishe Shtime, 1941; cuid12610 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Difunde en la emigracion el movimiento comunista de espana, 1974; cuid12611 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Eye - The Martin Lawrence Gazette, 1935; cuid12612 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Fourth International Bulletins, 1937; cuid12613 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Information Bulletin, 1968; cuid12614 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - International Bulletin of the Fourth International, 1960; cuid12615 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Jeune Taupe!, 1975; cuid12616 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Labor Action, 1951; cuid12617 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Little Red School House: Houston, TX, 1970; cuid12618 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Marxist-Leninist Forward, 1977; cuid12619 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Michigan Militant Newsletter: Detroit, MI, 1959-1961; cuid12620 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Neues Deginnen Baetter Internationaler Sozialisten, 1953; cuid12621 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement miscellaneous dispatches and newsletters, 1974-1975; cuid12622 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - New Banner, 1947; cuid12623 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - New Foundation: Lawrence, MA, 1969-1970; cuid12624 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - New Socialist [leaflet]: Warren, MI, circa 2000s; cuid12625 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - New York Organizer, 1944; cuid12626 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - New York Socialist and Trades Union Review: New York, NY, 1903; cuid12627 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - New York Telegram, 1953; cuid12628 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - News and Letters, 1980; cuid12629 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - One Small Step Forward - Statement by Jim + Grace Lee Boggs and Freddie + Lyman Paine on Cannon and Trotskyism, circa 1960s; cuid12630 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Order Out Of Chaos, circa 1940s; cuid12631 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - People Get Ready: Cleveland, OH, 1973-1975; cuid12632 (Box 156, Folder 9-10)
  - People's Canada Daily News Release, 1972; cuid12633 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Perspectives and Tasks of the Trotskyist Organizing Committee, 1975; cuid12634 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Polemicist, 1990; cuid12635 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Quantum: An Independent Marxist Newspaper: Aberdeen, SD, 1972; cuid12636 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Red Times, 1970; cuid12637 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Reorient Papers, circa 1970s; cuid12638 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Resolution: Auf Initiative der "Proletarischen Aktion", circa 1980s; cuid12639 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Revolutionary Press, 1977; cuid12640 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Revolutionnaire Russie, 1925; cuid12641 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Robotnik (The Worker), 1989; cuid12642 (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - Service d'information et de presse, 1936; cuid12643 (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - Socialist: San Francisco, CA, 1895; cuid12644 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Socialist International Women Bulletin, circa 2000s; cuid12645 (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - Socialist Organizer Review: San Francisco, CA, 1995; cuid12646 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Union and the Second Special Session of the United Nations General Assembly on Disarmament/The USSR's Food Program for the Period Ending in 1990 and Measures for It's Implementation, circa 1990s; cuid12647 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Spark: Amherst, MA, circa 1970s; cuid12648 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Spartacist [reprint], 1965; cuid12649 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Stalinism and Bolshevism, 1937; cuid12650 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Stenographic Report...Trotskyism in the USA, circa 1970s; cuid12651 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - The Australian Communist, circa 1980s; cuid12652 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Trenton Rank & File: Trenton, NJ, 1975; cuid12653 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-Ninth National Convention, 1976; cuid12654 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Wayne Socialist, 1956; cuid12655 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - What's to be done, 1978; cuid12656 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Wisconsin Commonwealth, 1949-1950; cuid12657 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Worker & Soldier: New York, NY, 1970-1971; cuid12658 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - YSA Organizer, 1972, 1978-1979; cuid12659 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - New Broadside: Broadside, New York, NY, 1967, 1970; cuid13320 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Young Worker: Young Workers Communist League of America / Young Workers Liberation League, New York, New York, 1929-1930, 1970-1979, 1981-1983; cuid13323 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Internal Discussion Bulletin: Fourth Internationalist Tendency, Brooklyn, NY, 1984; cuid13324 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Israel in Crisis: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1950; cuid13327 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - The Dock Worker: The Communist Party Dock Nucleus Savannah and Morgan Lines, New York, New York, 1935; cuid13328 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Theses and Decisions of the Thirteenth Plenum of the E.C.C.I.: Workers Library Publishers / Executive Communist International, New York, NY, 1933; cuid13329 (Box 199, Folder 13)
  - Activist (New York): The New York Area W.E.B. Du Bois Clubs, New York, NY, 1966-1968; cuid13330 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - The United Front Against War and Fascism: Gamma Publishing Co., New York, NY, 1974; cuid13333 (Box 199, Folder 15)
  - New American Movement Discussion: New American Movement, Minneapolis, MN, 1974-1975; cuid13334 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Report on the Committee of Education: AFL-CIO, New York, NY, circa 1970-1979; cuid13335 (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - "Winning the Masses for United States Revolution": The Committee for Political Science, New York, NY, 1967; cuid13338 (Box 199, Folder 16)
  - SFCC Bulletin: San Francisco Committee for Correspondence, San Francisco, California, 1948; cuid13339 (Box 199, Folder 12)
  - New Review: Grenich Printing Corporation / New Review, New York, NY, 1942-1944; cuid13342 (Box 200, Folder 1-2, Box 201)
  - Butte Socialist: Socialist Party County Committee, Butte, MT, 1915; cuid13344 (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - SWP Bulletins: Socialist Workers Party: New York, NY, 1937-1952; cuid13345 (Box 193, Folder 1, Box 194, Box 195, Folder 1-2)
  - Labor Power: Greenwood Reprint Corporation, Westport, Connecticut, 1939-1949; cuid13347 (Box 196, Folder 1-2)